{
    "v1.76": [
        {
            "question": "What new features are included in Comfyroll Studio version v1.76?",
            "answer": "CR VAE Decode, CR Combine Prompt and CR Diamond Pattern were added."
        }
    ],
    "v1.75.1": [
        {
            "question": "What issues were addressed in Comfyroll Studio version v1.75.1?",
            "answer": "Issue 112 with CR Text Blacklist was fixed, adding handling for blank lines and fixing the problem with finding multiple keywords. In addition, PR108 fixed a missing import in 'nodes_utils_text.py'.",
            "subject": "Comfyroll Studio"
        }
    ],
    "v1.75": [
        {
            "question": "What was added to Comfyroll Studio in version v1.75?",
            "answer": "CR Half Drop Panel was added."
        }
    ],
    "v1.74.1": [
        {
            "question": "What was the fix in Comfyroll Studio version v1.74.1?",
            "answer": "The issue with the CR Thumbnail Preview show_help was fixed."
        }
    ],
    "v1.74": [
        {
            "question": "What updates were made to Comfyroll Studio in version v1.74?",
            "answer": "CR Simple Image Compare was updated to automatically resize the second image if the size is different. New nodes, CR Aspect Ratio For Print and CR Seamless Checker, were added. A node to select ISO Size, CR Select ISO Size, was also added."
        }
    ],
    "v1.73.1": [
        {
            "question": "What was fixed in Comfyroll Studio version v1.73.1?",
            "answer": "The issue 104 was fixed."
        }
    ],
    "v1.73": [
        {
            "question": "What are the updates in Comfyroll Studio version v1.73?",
            "answer": "CR String to Boolean was added, and CR Aspect Ratio Social Media was updated with more options. CR Color Tint was updated to fix a color issue."
        }
    ],
    "v1.72": [
        {
            "question": "What were the features added in Comfyroll Studio version v1.72?",
            "answer": "CR Select Resize Method and CR Set Switch From String were added."
        }
    ],
    "v1.71.1": [
        {
            "question": "What were the fixes in Comfyroll Studio version v1.71.1?",
            "answer": "Issues 101 (CR Select Font) and 103 (CR Overlay Transparent Image) were fixed."
        }
    ],
    "v1.71": [
        {
            "question": "What change was made to text util nodes in Comfyroll Studio version v1.71?",
            "answer": "The output of string outputs was changed to any_type."
        }
    ]
}